<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvTitle"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:maxLines="1"
        android:layout_margin="10dp"
        android:textSize="40dp"
        android:fontFamily="sans-serif-black"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:text="공지입니다"/>


    <CheckBox
        android:id="@+id/iv_game_popup_not_again"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="55dp"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_margin="12dp"
        android:button="@drawable/cf_blt_check2cafe"
        android:paddingStart="8dp"
        android:text="오늘은 그만 보기"
        android:textSize="15dp"
        android:textColor="@color/white1"
        tools:ignore="RtlSymmetry" />

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/iv_game_popup_close"
        android:layout_width="40dp"
        android:layout_height="40dp"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_margin="13dp"
        android:src="@drawable/cf_icon_win_close" />

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_margin="40dp"
        android:layout_above="@id/iv_game_popup_close"
        android:layout_below="@id/tvTitle">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"

            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"

                android:text="반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하 반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하 반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하 반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하 반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하 반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하반가워요 헬로 에브리 바디 콜라 콜라 하하하하하"
                android:textSize="18dp" />

        </LinearLayout>



    </ScrollView>


</RelativeLayout>
